(Katee Sackhoff:)George, let me
ask you something.
(Katee Sackhoff:)How did you deal
with being typecast
(Katee Sackhoff:)as a science fiction icon?
(George Takei:)It's difficult.
(George Takei:)You try and stretch
as an actor--
(George Takei:)do Strindberg, O'Neill,
(George Takei:)but all they want is,
"Course laid in, Captain."
(Katee Sackhoff:)Tell me about it.
(Katee Sackhoff:)It's frackin'
frustrating.
(Howard:)Wait. Katee,
why are you leaving?
(Bernadette:)She's leaving because you
really want to be with me.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, I found my girdle!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)It was in the dryer!
(Howard:)Great, Ma!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)I think it shrunk!
(Mrs Wolowitz:)I'm spilling out like
the Pillsbury Doughboy here!
(Howard:)And with that mental picture,
(Howard:)I think we're done
for the evening.
(Leonard:)You know, you never
told me what happened
(Leonard:)between you
and Bernadette.
(Howard:)I did a stupid thing.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I guessed that.
(Howard:)It was the kind of thing